



Nikolaiev Mykhailo

Front-End developer

O Ukraine, Kyiv

☑ ab3mn3@gmail.com

% +38-066-800-79-85

SOCIAL

in/mykhailo-nikolaiev

nab3MN

</>/> Codewars

EDUCATION

Thermal power engineer

Kyiv energy college 2006-2010

Thermal power engineer

Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute 2014-2018

SKILLS

JavaScript

• HTML

TypeScript

• CSS

• React/Redux

• Nodejs(Express)

MongoDB

• SASS

SOFT SKILLS

- Analytical
- Innovative
- Proactive
- Creative
- · Self-starting

Detailed

• Adaptable

PROFILE

Courteous and enthusiastic, I am interested in IT. I recently began to be fascinated by web programming, e.g. developing apps and building websites. I am keen to gain more experience in the field. For this reason, I am looking for a company willing to offer me a placement among their developers. In return, I would offer my full commitment, and be a pleasant and friendly addition to your team. I am therefore currently looking for a job or an internship as a front-end developer. My objective is to become a middle within one years.

EXPERIENCE

Main storekeeper

From 2021 to Present | NEXUS ENGINEERING

Storekeeper

From 2018 to 2019 | Kasta

Mechanic of machine shop

From 2014 to 2018 | Kyiv Electric Train Repair Plant

PORTFOLIO

Commercial Project

Pet project:React/Redux/Node/Express/MongoDB:

BackEnd for pet project (Express, MongoDB)

Travel: React/Adeptive Design:

News,posts,movie,weather seacher: React/Redux/TypeScript/AJAX:

CV: Adeptive Design(html,css,js)

LANGUAGES

• Ukraine • Russian

• English(Pre-Intermediate)

INTERESTS

Music	₹ Travel	Book
4 ⊢}	ů	*
Gym	Study	Walk